{"questions":[{"question":"Arrange in the order of 5 levels of maturity","answer":"Siloed, Simplified, Scaled, Synergized, Self-Optimized"},{"question":"What are the Key Focus Areas of DATOM","answer":"All of the these"},{"question":"Are there specific visualizations available in DATOM to track the DG Metrics","answer":"No"},{"question":"What is the core principle of DATOM?","answer":"There is no single solution in Data & Analytics space. A fabric of solutions needs to be woven."},{"question":"What is the difference between Data Owner and Data Steward?","answer":"Data Steward controls the data quality on a day to day basis for a data set"},{"question":"Which is not a Key Result Areas in DATOM?","answer":"Roadmap"},{"question":"Which of the following aspects of EA includes Process Aligned KPIs, Data Models, Metadata Mgmt., DQ Mgmt., MDM, ILM & Data Security?","answer":"Information Architecture"},{"question":"In DATOM, COD is?","answer":"Competency on Demand"},{"question":"_____ is TCS' CoD platforms?","answer":"Fresco Play"},{"question":"What is data driven culture","answer":"All the options mentioned"},{"question":"What is the theme of 5th maturity level ?","answer":"Universal Intelligence"},{"question":"Identify a business question that can be answered only by Level 5 matured organization.","answer":"Do you collect social data on your partners to assess their market reputation, are any insights generated on this to help with contract negotiations?"},{"question":"Zachman Framework has been used by DATOM to ?","answer":"To identify alignment between different service delivery methodologies"},{"question":"The solution ccelertor for Digitised data controls is","answer":"DIME"},{"question":"DATOM conceptual \"Big Picture\" contains","answer":"All the options mentioned "},{"question":"What is the maturity level of a company which has implemented Big Data Cloudification, Recommendation Engine Self Service, Machine Learning, Agile & Factory model ?","answer":"4ml"},{"question":"For a Level 2 matured organization, which statement is true from Master Data Management perspective?","answer":"Master Data is elevated to the Enterprise level, with mechanism to manage and access it."},{"question":"Data Ownership is defined by","answer":"Any of options based on scale of the organization"},{"question":"As per DATOM, which of the following options best describes Unstructured DQ Mgmt.?","answer":"Gather-Analyze-Recommend X Data Quality Index X"}]}